Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), 1987-2015; 6; 2.8 cubic ft.
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty and Delaware Citizens Opposed to the Death Penalty (DCODP)/ Delaware Repeal, ca. 2013 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 97)
  - Nanon Williams, 2010 November - December (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 98)
  - National Program Strategy, 1998 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 99)
  - Notes from the ED Meeting in Louisville, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 100)
  - Overview of the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, ca. 2011 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 101)
  - Performance Appraisal Schedule and Form, ca. 2010 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 102)
  - Personnel Policies and Procedure Manual, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 103)
  - Press Release, 2005 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 104)
  - Press Release - Chicago Tribune, 2006 June 24 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 105)
  - Press Release on Connecticut Network to Abolish the Death Penalty Join Efforts of NCADP, 2012 April 11 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 106)
  - Program Coordinator Position Description, 1996 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 107)
  - Program Slides on State Assessment, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Communications Goals and Activities, 2013 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 2)
  - Rachel King Fund, 2009; 2011 January 8; Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 3)
  - Rachel King Fund Meeting Agenda, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 4)
  - Racial Disparities and Racial Discrimination in Capital Sentencing in the United States, 2001 July (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 5)
  - Reaching for the Dream, National Conference - San Jose, California Packet, 2008 January 17-20 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 6)
  - Recruitment on Law Enforcement for a Moratorium on Executions, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 7)
  - Reimbrusement Requests, 2004 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 8)
  - Remarks at the Southern Center of Human Rights Frederick Douglass Awards Dinner by Anthony G. Amsterdam, 2008 October 2 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 9)
  - Report to the Board, 2009 September (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 10)
  - Request for Support from Rust-Tierney, ca. 2015 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 11)
  - Requesting Affiliate's Information and Surveys, 2009 April - May (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 12)
  - "Restoring Justice, Reclaiming Humanity" Conference - Chicago, Illinois, 2002 October 24-27 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 13)
  - Retreat Agenda, 2012 March 14-15 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 14)
  - Retreat Flip Chart Notes, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 15)
  - "Revisiting the Death Penalty: 30 Years After Gregg" - Communication Plan Prepared by Brenda Bowser Soder, Communications Director, DPIC David Elliot, Communications Director NCADP, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 16)
  - Senior Field Organizer, Position Description ca. 2013 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 17)
  - Shouting From the Rooftops, 2009 October 7; 2010 January 12 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 18)
  - Special Telephone Call from NCADP for State Affiliates Script, 2010 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 19)
  - Staff Meeting Agenda, 2008 October 20; 2011 February 24 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 20)
  - Staff Meeting Materials, 2009 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 21)
  - Staff Request Agenda, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 22)
  - Staff Plan For "Training For the Long Run", 2011 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 23)
  - State Affiliates Training Call, 2010 October 27 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 24)
  - State Assessment Meeting, 2009 July 9 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 25)
  - Statistics Regarding NCADP's Internet and Social Media Outreach, 2009 September 17 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 26)
  - Strategic and Operational Plan Update Faciltated by John D. Baker, Strategies for the Future, 2009 January 29 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 27)
  - Strategic Planning Meeting Minutes, 1999 June 25 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 28)
  - Summary for Proposed Bylaw Revision and Voting Ballots, 2006 October (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 29)
  - Survey Results, Member Organizations 2013 Priority, Capacity, and Target States (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 30)
  - Talking Points Regarding the Presidential Elections and the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 31)
  - Tennessee and the New South: Organizing for Abolition, 2003 October 16 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 32)
  - Texas Campaign Director Job Announcement, 2010 Februrary 4 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 33)
  - Texas / Virginia Staff Plan, 2010 February 3 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 34)
  - Tours of Available Properties Provided by Audra Cunningham, 2012 October 9 (Box 3 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 35)
  - Tough Questions Workshop Questions and Conversation Topics, Undated (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 1)
  - Training Conference Call Schedule and Notes, 2009 March 26 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 2)
  - Training for Long Run, 2011 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 3)
  - Training for Long Run Awards Dinner, 2009 January 24 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 4)
  - Training for the Long Run- Annual Conference -Harrisburg, Pennsylvania Program, 2009 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 5)
  - Training for the Long Run, Conference Welcome Statement by Diann Rust- Tierney, Executive Director, 2009 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 6)
  - Training for the Long Run- Louisville, Kentucky, 2010 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 7)
  - Training for the Long Run Awards Dinner Program, 2010 January 16 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 8)
  - Training Staff Meeting Agenda and Notes, 2009 August 10 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 9)
  - Training and Staff Meeting Notes, 2009 July (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 10)
  - Training Structure Overview and Goals, 2009 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 11)
  - Training Tools- Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute, Catholic University of America, 2008 August 6-8 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 12)
  - Turning Wins into Winning Conference Media Plan, 2005 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 13)
  - Turning Wins into Winning Conference Program, 2005 October 27-30 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 14)
  - "Turning Wins into Winning" Awards Banquet Speaker Bios, 2005 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 15)
  - "Turning Wins into Winning" Conference Program and Press Releases, 2005 October (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 16)
  - Update on NCADP Activities from Diann Rust-Tierney, 2007 February 12 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 17)
  - "Utilizing Volunteers and Interns Effectively" Presented by Katie Campbell, Skye Consulting, 2009 October 27 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 18)
  - Working with "Voices of Experience" As A Campaign Tactic, Undated (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 19)
  - 25th Anniversary National Conference "Building Communities of Justice and Hope", 2001 October 18-21 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 20)
  - A 30th Anniversary History by Eugene G. Wanger, 2006 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 21)
  - 35th Anniversary ToolKit: Building a Movement of Justice in Every State, Undated (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 22)
  - 35 Years of Building a Movement for Justice, Press Package, Board of Directors Meeting, 2012 May 12 (Box 4 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 23)
- Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (CUADP), 1997-2005; 7; 0.4 cubic ft.
  Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Penalty was an organization that Abe founded. The movement was based in Gainesville, Florida and focused primarily on Floridians on Death Row. CUADP had close ties with the state abolitionist group in Florida, Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (FADP).
  - Abolitionwear Catalog, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 1)
  - Abolitionwear Ordering Informaiton, 2001 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 2)
  - The Abolitionist Action Committee, 1997 June 14 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 3)
  - Announcement CUADP is Moving to Gainesville, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 4)
  - CUADP- Celebration of 150th Anniversary of Michigan Abolishing the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 5)
  - Center on Crimes Community and Culture (CCCC) Program Grant Proposal, 1997 May 22 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 6)
  - Caesar Chavez Pin and Juan Melendez Articles, 2003 June 1 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 7)
  - Contract Information and Notes, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 8)
  - Coral Gables Congregational Church Grant Proposal, 2002 Novemeber (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 9)
  - CUADP- Death Penalty Brown Bag Lunch Series, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 10)
  - Declaration of Abraham J. Bonowitz On Behalf of CUADP, 2002 September 3 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 11)
  - CUADP - Email List, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 12)
  - Fact Sheets About the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 13)
  - Gainesville Citizens for Alternatives to the Death Penalty Meeting Minutes, 2005 February (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 14)
  - Kraut, Nine to Abe Bonowitz, 2000 February 4 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 15)
  - Life V. Death, A One Hour Documentary Film on the History of Capital Punishment in America, undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 16)
  - Letter from Christine Borgeson with Questions, 2005 February 10 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 17)
  - List of Donors With Their Total Donations, 2005 February 3 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 18)
  - Meeting Agenda and Materials, 1999 February 3 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 19)
  - CUADP- NCADP's Response to CUADP, 1997 February 25 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 20)
  - CUADP- News Clippings, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 21)
  - Newsletters, 1999-2006 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 22)
  - Not In My Name Program, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 23)
  - Pelke, Bill, Thank You, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 24)
  - Press Releases: Annual Fast and Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1999 July 2; 2000 June 29 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 25)
  - Press Release from Floridians Against the Death Penalty (FADP) and Related Materials, 2003 December (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 26)
  - CUADP Rally Publicity, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 27)
  - Registration Forms for 10th Annual Fast and Vigil "Starvin' for Justice", 2003 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 28)
  - Registration Forms for 12th Annual Fast and Vigil "Starvin' for Justice", 2005 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 29)
  - Requieme for Frank Lee Smith- PBS Special Announcement, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 30)
  - Resources for Planning, 1997; 1998 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 31)
  - Sample Thank-You Letters, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 32)
  - Scrapbook, 2003; 2005 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 33)
  - Lambrix v. Dugger- VSDC, FL.- Petitioners Pro Se Written Objections to Courts Report and Recommendation, Sheppard, Samuel Reece Rally Materials and Media Advisory, 2000 February 9 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 34)
  - CUADP Special Meeting Agenda on SJR 124, 2001 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 35)
  - "Stop Executions" Flyer, Ca. 1997 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 36)
  - Testimonies of Samuel Reece Sheppard and George W. White Before the DC City Council, 1997 June 25 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 37)
  - CUADP Thank You Note from A. Bonowitz, 2004 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 38)
  - "Time for Death Penalty Moratorium is Past Due" by Abraham J. Bonowitz in The Tampa Tribune, 2000 December 23 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 39)
  - CUADP Update, 1999 Summer (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 40)
  - "Vote No On #2" Flyer to Fight Amendment #2, Undated (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 41)
  - 4th Annual Fast and Vigil to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1997 July 2 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 42)
  - 6th Annual Fast and Vigil "Starvin' for Justice '99" Rally Against the Death Penalty, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Citizens United for Alternatives to the Death Pena), Folder 43)
- New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (NJADP), 2000-2012; 8; 1.2 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged chronologically and contains a variety of documents and publications all related to the successful abolition campaign conducted in New Jersey beginning in the early 2000s. Materials include notices for NJADP-sponsored speaker events at various public venues and churches, samples of mass mailings, administrative materials for coordinating events by New Jersey legislative districts and a variety of other items generated by Abe Bonowitz over the course of NJADPs multi-year campaign.
  - NJAC Personnel Manual, 2000 July 1 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 1)
  - White Paper on The Death Penalty Position on The Death Penalty NJDPM, 2002 March (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 2)
  - "New Jerseyans Opinions on a Death Penalty Moratorium", 2002 May (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 3)
  - New Jersey Law Journal, 2004 February 23 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 4)
  - Thank-you from Senator Shirley Turner to Celeste Fitzgerald and NJADP, 2004 October 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 5)
  - League of Women Voters of New Jersey "Ending The Death Penalty in New Jersey" Brochure, 2004 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with members of Legislature from NJADP Members and Affiliates, 2004; 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 7)
  - Unsorted Abolition Event Flyers, 2004-2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 8)
  - New Jersey Association on Correction Consultant from for A. Bonowitz/NJADP, 2005 March (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 9)
  - Celeste Fitzgerald to-do list A. Bonowitz, 2005 April 16 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 10)
  - NJADP Members letter, 2005 July (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 11)
  - Legislative Rosfer and NJADP Member E-mail, 2005 August (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Philantropies Grant Proposal, 2005 August 1 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 13)
  - NJADP Mass Member Mailing to Petition Representatives, 2005 Fall (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 14)
  - "Money for Nothing? The Financial Cost of New Jersey's Death Penalty", 2005 November (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 15)
  - Helen Prejean faith in action Day NJ Statehouse, 2005 December 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 16)
  - NJADP Speaker event and Mass Calling Material, 2005 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 17)
  - NJ Legislator Profiles, 2005 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 18)
  - "Innocence Lost in NJ", Circa 2005 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 19)
  - Opinion Letter of Rev. Kevin Keelen, 2006 January 18 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 20)
  - NJADP Field Manager Job Descriptions, 2006 February 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 21)
  - NJADP Organizing Goals, 2006; 2006-2-28 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 22)
  - Unifarian Universalist Congregation of Somerset Hills "Not in my Name", 2006 April 9 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 23)
  - 212 NJ Legislature Legislative Leadership and committee membership informational Packet, 2006 April 25 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 24)
  - NADP Press Release Re: Judiciary Committee Passing Bill 5-171, 2006 May 10 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 25)
  - NJADP Presentation of Adult Faith Formation Event, 2006 May 18 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 26)
  - "The Death Penalty and a Consistent Ethic of Life," NJADP Panel Program, 2006 May 23 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 27)
  - New Jersey Council of Churches 62nd Annual Dinner Program, 2006 June 6 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 28)
  - Whippany Conference Correspondence, 2006 June 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 29)
  - NJADP Tables at Bruce Springsteen Tour locations in New Jersey, 2006 June 15 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 30)
  - Legislative District Material Gathered by Bonowitz Before DP Study Commision meeting, 2006 July 10 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 31)
  - NJADP Correspondence re: Friends Meeting Event, 2006 July 26 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 32)
  - A. Bonowitz To-Do List, 2006 August 14 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 33)
  - J TVI Events Listing, 2006 August 23 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 34)
  - Brandeis Society/Innocence Project forum event Program, 2006 August 24 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 35)
  - NJAC Consultant Contracts, 2006 August (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 36)
  - September 2007 Study Commission hearing notices, 2006 September 13; 2006 September 27 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 37)
  - NJADP September Swing Press Clips, 2006 September 15-21 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 38)
  - Sr. Helen Prejean event Email Organizing details, 2006 September 26 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 39)
  - Dr. Trudy Conway to Celeste Fitzgerald Re: NJADP Participation in Confrence, 2006 September 28 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 40)
  - A. Bonowitz to NJ Council of Churches Re: Advertisement form for NCADP Conference, 2006 September 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 41)
  - Workshop on Death Penalty Abolition Programming Tentative Itinerary, 2006 September 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 42)
  - Journeys through Violence and Injustice September 2006 Events and Planning, 2006 September (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 43)
  - NJADP Flyers fpr Judiciary Hearings, 2006 September (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 44)
  - NJADP Membership Mailing, 2006 September (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 45)
  - "Life without Parole, Our other Death Penalty", 2006 October 22 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 46)
  - Revised Public Hearing notice New Jersey Death Penalty Study Comission, 2006 October 25 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 47)
  - NJADP Media Advisory, 2006 October (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 48)